{
  "quizName": "Hollow Knight",
  "randomize": true,
  "accountID": 1,
  "questions": [
      {
          "questionNum": 1,
          "question": "How many nailmasters are there?",
          "correctAnswer": "3",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "2",
              "1",
              "4"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 2,
          "question": "To which Dreamer was Quirrel apprenticed?",
          "correctAnswer": "Monomon",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "Lurien",
              "Herrah",
              ""
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 3,
          "question": "Who is the daughter of the Pale King and Herrah the Beast?",
          "correctAnswer": "Hornet",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "Tiso",
              "Quirrel",
              "Zote the Mighty"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 4,
          "question": "How many opportunities do you have to let Zote die?",
          "correctAnswer": "2",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "4",
              "1",
              "0"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 5,
          "question": "What is the Pure Completion achievement for?",
          "correctAnswer": "Achieve 112% completion",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "ascending the Pantheon of Hallownest",
              "Aiding the Herald in moving on",
              "collecting 2400 Essence and hearing the Seer's final words"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 6,
          "question": "Which NPC is associated with two conflicting achievements?",
          "correctAnswer": "Zote",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "Hornet",
              "Quirrel",
              "Cloth"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 7,
          "question": "What is the final boss of the game?",
          "correctAnswer": "Absolute Radiance",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "The Godseeker (Pale King)",
              "Pure Vessel",
              "Nightmare King Grimm"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 8,
          "question": "Which additional content pack was released last?",
          "correctAnswer": "Godmaster",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "Hidden Dreams",
              "The Grimm Troupe",
              "Lifeblood"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 9,
          "question": "Which NPC from the original is the main character in the sequel Silksong?",
          "correctAnswer": "Hornet",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "Zote the Mighty",
              "Quirrel",
              "The Hollow Knight"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 10,
          "question": "Who is Hornet's half-sibling?",
          "correctAnswer": "The Knight",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "Zote the Mighty",
              "Cloth",
              "Quirrel"
          ]
      }
  ]
}